Finding Aid for James V. Mansfield Papers
William L. Clements Library, University of Michigan
- Volume 30: 13 Loose items, 1859 November 18-1877 July 8, undated
Women--Appearance
1: 108-109
2: 219
3: 50, 79-80
4: 30-33
5: 107-109, 153
6: 6-8
7: 101-102
10: 81-82
14: 88-91
17: 32-37, 83-84, 172-175, 306-307, 376-380
20: 339-343
21: 237
22: 151-152
Women--California
1: 105
2: 219, 261-262
3: 51-52, 178-179
6: 6-8
9: 80
11: 161
13: 478
14: 88-91
17: 32-37, 172-175, 306-307
19: 76, 96
21: 377-378
22: 151-152, 266-286, 344
Women--Social conditions
15: 283-285
22: 130-131, 266-268
23: 284
24: 41-46, 184
Women mediums
13: 26-27, 69-75, 179, 407
14: 154
16: 266
24: 149
27: 801
See also Britten, Emma Hardinge
Working class--California--San Francisco--Social conditions
1: 39-40
16: 72
22: 266-268
24: 41-46
27: 525-527
Partial Name Index
Andrew, John Albion, 1818-1867
10: 17-18
16: 37
Beecher, Henry Ward, 1813-1887
4: 132-133
Beecher, Lyman, 1775-1863
14: 79
27: 510
Bellows, Henry Whitney, 1814-1882
26: 458
27: 138
Britten, Emma Hardinge, 1823-1899
Passim, but especially
1: 120
2: 35, 87
3: 94-95, 170-171
5: 26-28, 238-240
13: 68-69
15: 231, 399-402
25: passim
26: 319
Brown, Charles Farrar (Artemus Ward), 1834-1867
1: 236
25: 28, 93
Brown, John, 1800-1859
9: 40-41
Brownlow, William Gannaway, 1805-1877
4: 10-11
Butler, Benjamin F., 1818-1893
10: 17-18
Child, Asaph Bemis, 1813-1879
2: 77
13: 53, 246-248, 441-442
15: 40
Davis, Andrew Jackson, 1826-1910
4: 201
Davis, Jefferson, 1808-1889
21: 41
26: 475
Edwards, Amasa, 1814-1885
passim
Edwards, Matilda "Mattie", 1821-1884
passim
Estabrook, Col.
passim
Estabrook, Hattie
passim
Farnham, Eliza, 1815-1864
1: 173
Fitch, Col. Henry S.
21: 2-8
25: 109-110
Forster, Thomas Gales, 1816-1886
2: 43-44, 62
Fremont, John Charles, 1813-1890
5: 191-199
Grant, Ulysses S., 1822-1885
21: 127
27: 377
Hooker, Joseph, 1814-1879
17: 467-468
20: 72-76
Kalakaua I, 1836-1891
June 20, 1874
January 2, 1875
King, Edith, b.c. 1851
27: 796-797
King, Julia Wiggin, b.c. 1828
3: 167-169
13: 526-527
22: 312-314
23: 397-399
26: 357-358
King, Thomas Starr, 1824-1864
Passim, but especially
2: 229
3: 5-9, 128-130, 165-172
4: 75-79, 94-98, 130-133
6: 52-55, 69
7: 44-45, 94
8: 55-57, 68-69
9: 66-70, 156-159
10: 20-21, 113-115
14: 1-5
15: 57, 350-366, 425-432
18: 21-22
19: 121
20: 44
25: 427, 432-433
26: 291-303, 319, 509
Lee, Robert E., 1807-1870
21: 41, 146
Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865
1: 354-355
4: 151-152
15: 455-456
16: 67-68
26: 97
Lincoln, Mary Todd, 1818-1882
14: 165
Macondray, Capt. Frederick William, 1803-1862
4: 24-25
Mansfield, Bertie
July 8, 1877
Mansfield, Daniel
20: 29
Mansfield, James Valentine, b.c. 1817
passim
Mansfield, Jera M., b.c. 1825
passim
Mansfield, John Worthington, 1849-1933
3: 83
4: 39
6: 100
15: 3, 10-12, 149-150
19: 231
21: 141-142, 169-170, 231
23: 154-155, 158-164
24: 10-11, 241-242
25: 97, 279, 409
June 20, 1874
January 2, 1875
Mansfield, Mary Gertrude "Gertie", b.c. 1854
1: 296
2: 25
3: 79-80
10: 93
14: 88-89
15: 10-12, 151
17: 229-230, 376-380
20: 339-343
21: 237-238
23: 170
24: 104, 189
27: 259
November 18, 1859
April 27, 1860
Mansfield, Mary Hopkinson, b.c. 1827
passim
Mansfield, Ellen "Nellie" Greenwood Estabrook, b.c. 1836
passim
Mansfield, Walter D., b.c. 1860
11: 41
McClellan, George Brinton, 1826-1885
6: 50
8: 144
McClellan, R. Guy
10: 71-76
13: 497-498
McDougal, Governor John, 1818-1866
2: 10, 22-27, 68-69, 73
Montez, Lola, 1821-1861
13: 26-27
Napoleon III (Charles Louis Napoleon Bonaparte), 1808-1873
21: 73-75
22: 179, 210-213
23: 355
24: 262
Owen, James Jerome, 1827-1895
2: 71-72
5: 43-48
7: 72-74, 98
Peebles, James Martin, 1822-1922
12: 123
Rowe, Gen. George
3: 10, 279-280, 350-352, 389-395, 405-409
Stow, Marietta L., d. 1902
13: 69-75, 179, 407
14: 154
Stidger, O.B.
27: 352, 465-470
Strickland, Edward F.
passim
Twiggs, David Emanuel, 1790-1862
6: 112
Young, Brigham, 1801-1877
8: 16
15: 15-16
Partial Geographical Index
Alcatraz Island, California
6: 13-18
Baltimore, Maryland
November 18, 1859
Benicia, California
12: 24-25
Boston, Massachusetts
4: 131
Chelsea, Massachusetts
passim
Denver, Colorado
July 8, 1877
Grass Valley, California
13: 5
Marysville, California
11
12: 46-47, 96-99
Napa, California
11: 41-42, 48-50, 67, 107
19: 178
New York City, New York
passim
Paris, France
June 18, 1874: 42-43
Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
April 27, 1860
Sacramento, California
2: 62
San Francisco, California
passim
Sierra Nevada Mountains, California
12: 46-47
Sonoma, California
22: 207
Virginia City, Nevada
27: pasim
Washoe County, Nevada
passim
Yuba County, California
13: 418